Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - G
        - Gordon, Billy - Billy Gordon plays lovers' hits, 1973; SR-16273; Gordon, Billy (Box 281)
          Catalog # PAS 6057; A-side Matrix # PAS-6057-A-2
          Paramount Records
        - Gordon, Lonnie - Do you want it, 1994; SR-16274; Gordon, Lonnie (Box 281)
          Catalog # CR-304-DJ; A-side Matrix # CR-304-A
        - Gordon, Lonnie - Dirty love, 1996; SR-16275; Gordon, Lonnie (Box 281)
          Catalog # REP5-0002; A-side Matrix # REP5-0002-A
          Republic Records
        - Gordon, Lonnie - Gonna catch you, 1991; SR-16276; Gordon, Lonnie (Box 281)
          Catalog # V-19743; A-side Matrix # V-19743A
          SBK Records
        - Gorillaz - Clint Eastwood, 2001; SR-16277; Gorillaz (Box 281)
          Catalog # 12R 6552; A-side Matrix # 8790505 1A1 12R6552
          Parlophone
        - Görl, Robert - Darling don't leave me (extended mix), 1983; SR-16278; Görl, Robert (Box 281)
          Catalog # 12 MUTE 31; A-side Matrix # 12 MUTE 031 A
          Mute
        - Gorr, Jon - It's no lie, 1983; SR-16279; Gorr, Jon (Box 281)
          Catalog # MR 1001; A-side Matrix # MR-1001-A
          Massmedia Records
          Allston, Massachusetts
        - Gospel Gangstaz - I can see clearly now, 1999; SR-16280; Gospel Gangstaz (Box 281)
          Catalog # INT8P 6615; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6615-A-1
        - Got'ti, John - Cut throat; Put it on me; Scarred, 2001; SR-16281; Got'ti, John (Box 281)
          Catalog # 75766 70514 17; A-side Matrix # 75766 70514 17 A
          Big pocket Records
          New Orleans, Louisiana
        - Goulet, Michelle - Stop & think, 1986; SR-16282; Goulet, Michelle (Box 281)
          Catalog # DMD 943; A-side Matrix # STDM-49610-3 1-1
        - Goulet, Michelle - Over and over and over, 1988; SR-16283; Goulet, Michelle (Box 281)
          Catalog # PR 2239; A-side Matrix # STDM-53993-1
        - Goulet, Michelle - Stop & think, 1986; SR-16284; Goulet, Michelle (Box 281)
          Catalog # 0-96814; A-side Matrix # STDM-49610-3 1-1
        - Goulet, Michelle - Stop & think, 1986; SR-16285; Goulet, Michelle (Box 281)
        - Governor - Dirty south, 1999; SR-16286; Governor (Box 281)
          Catalog # WR-271-1DJ; A-side Matrix # WR-272-1A
          Warlock
        - GP Wu - 1st things first; If you only knew; Hip hop, 1998; SR-16287; GP Wu (Box 281)
          Catalog # MCA8P-4143; A-side Matrix # MCA 13120-SIDE ONE
        - GQ - Standing ovation, 1979; SR-16288; GQ (Box 281)
          Catalog # CP-709; A-side Matrix # CP-709-Re-2-SA
        - GQ And The Funky Republic - Yo!!! The EP!!!, 1994; SR-16289; GQ And The Funky Republic (Box 281)
          Catalog # DIB0206; A-side Matrix # DIB-0209-A
          Dressed In Black
        - GQ - Make my dreams a reality, 1979; SR-16290; GQ (Box 281)
          Catalog # SP-58; A-side Matrix # SP58-SA-1B
        - GQ - Try smurfin', 1982; SR-16291; GQ (Box 281)
          Catalog # CP-724; A-side Matrix # CP-724-SA
        - GQ - Shake yo booty (boom), 1981; SR-16292; GQ (Box 281)
          Catalog # SP-117; A-side Matrix # SP117SAS-T2
        - G.Q. Steve - Movin'; We can do this, 1989; SR-16293; G.Q. Steve; D.J. Slice (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16294. Different discs.
          Catalog # TL 1003; A-side Matrix # TL-1003-A-RE1
          Thin-Lyne Records
          Long Beach, California
        - Heart To Heart - Judy's booty, 1991; SR-16294; Heart To Heart (Box 281)
          In same jacket as # SR-16293. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 1650; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-60154
          Interscope Records
        - GR8 TJ - FearinJah EP, 1998; SR-15202; GR8 TJ (Box 281)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # BEDROOM A
          Bedroom Records
        - Graeme L - Emerald, 2000; SR-16297; Graeme L (Box 281)
          Catalog # RNR 007; A-side Matrix # 08 42754 20 1E1 RNR 007
          Red 'n' Raw Recordings
          Edinburgh, United Kingdom
        - Graf Hadik - Biedermeier zorro groove, 1988; SR-16298; Graf Hadik (Box 281)
          Catalog # DUM 233 280; A-side Matrix # LP 233 280 A
          Dum Dum Records
          Austria
        - Grafh - Bang out, 2003; SR-16299; Grafh (Box 282)
          Catalog # EAS 54765; A-side Matrix # XSS-54765-A
        - Grafh - Bang out, 2003; SR-16300; Grafh (Box 282)
        - Graham Central Station - Graham Central Station, 1974; SR-16301; Graham Central Station (Box 282)
          Catalog # BS 2763; A-side Matrix # BS-2763 40689-1-2
        - Graham, Jaki - From now on, 1989; SR-16302; Graham, Jaki (Box 282)
          Catalog # D1-92835; A-side Matrix # D1-1-92835
          Orpheus Records
        - Graham, Jaki - Set me free, 1986; SR-16303; Graham, Jaki (Box 282)
          Catalog # V-15252; A-side Matrix # V1-15252-X601161-B
        - Graham, Jaki - Set me free, 1986; SR-16304; Graham, Jaki (Box 282)
        - Graham, Jaki - Breaking away, 1986; SR-16305; Graham, Jaki (Box 282)
          Catalog # EMC 3514; A-side Matrix # EMC 3514 A-1U-1-C
        - Graham, Jaki - From now on, 1989; SR-16306; Graham, Jaki (Box 282)
          Catalog # 12JAKI 15; A-side Matrix # 12 JAKI 1 3-1U-1-1
        - Graham, Jaki - Set me free, 1986; SR-16307; Graham, Jaki (Box 282)
        - Graham, Larry - Sooner or later, 1982; SR-16308; Graham, Larry (Box 282)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1046; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-1046-SH1
        - Graham, Larry - I'm sick and tired, 1983; SR-16309; Graham, Larry (Box 282)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2065; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-2065-SH2
        - Graham, Larry - I'm sick and tired, 1983; SR-16310; Graham, Larry (Box 282)
        - Graham, Tony - Kiss the boys, 1984; SR-16311; Graham, Tony (Box 282)
          Catalog # GRPT-109; A-side Matrix # GRP T 109 A
          Greyhound Record Productions
        - Grainger's - Shine your light, 1981; SR-16312; Grainger's (Box 282)
          Catalog # BC4009; A-side Matrix # BC-4009-A
          BC Records
        - Gramacks - Party party; Hot music (la fiesta), 1984; SR-16313; Gramacks; Joseph, Jeff (Box 282)
          Catalog # 821 062-1; A-side Matrix # 161 B210621 A
          R. Francis Entertainment
        - Gran Combo De Puerto Rico - Romantico y... Sabroso, 1988; SR-16314; Gran Combo De Puerto Rico (Box 282)
          Catalog # RCSLP 2054; A-side Matrix # RCSLP-2054-A
          Combo Records
        - Gran Combo De Puerto Rico - In Alaska: breaking the ice, 1984; SR-16315; Gran Combo De Puerto Rico (Box 282)
          Catalog # RCSLP 2039; A-side Matrix # COMBO-2039A
        - Gran Combo De Puerto Rico - Nuestra musica, 1988; SR-16316; Gran Combo De Puerto Rico (Box 282)
          Catalog # RCSLP 2045; A-side Matrix # RCSLP-2045-A
        - Gran Combo De Puerto Rico - Latin up, 1990; SR-16317; Gran Combo De Puerto Rico (Box 282)
          Catalog # RCSLP-2070; A-side Matrix # RCSLP-2070-A
        - Gran Combo De Puerto Rico - Nuestro aniversario, 1982; SR-16318; Gran Combo De Puerto Rico (Box 282)
          Catalog # RCSLP-2026; A-side Matrix # RCSLP-2026-A
        - Gran Combo De Puerto Rico - Happy days, 1981; SR-16319; Gran Combo De Puerto Rico (Box 282)
          Catalog # RCSLP 2021; A-side Matrix # COMBO-2021-A
        - Gran Combo De Puerto Rico - Disfrutelo hasta el cabo, 1974; SR-16320; Gran Combo De Puerto Rico (Box 282)
          Catalog # EGC 006; A-side Matrix # EGC LP 006 A
          EGC Records
        - Grand Agent - By design (Disc one), 2001; SR-16321; Grand Agent (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16322. Double album.
          Catalog # GAP 072; A-side Matrix # GAP 072 A
          Groove Attack Productions
        - Grand Agent - By design (Disc two), 2001; SR-16322; Grand Agent (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16321. Double album.
          Catalog # GAP 072; A-side Matrix # GAP 072 C
        - Grand Daddy I.U. - Don't stress me; Slinging bass, 1994; SR-16323; Grand Daddy I.U. (Box 282)
          Catalog # EAS 6048; A-side Matrix # XSS-6048-A-2A
          Epic Street
        - Grand Daddy I.U. - Represent (remixes), 1994; SR-16324; Grand Daddy I.U. (Box 282)
          Catalog # AED 6100; A-side Matrix # XSS-6100-A-1A
        - Grand Daddy I.U. - Lead pipe, 1994; SR-16325; Grand Daddy I.U. (Box 282)
          Catalog # E 57866; A-side Matrix # Al-5786-A-1A
        - Grand Daddy I.U. - Something new, 1990; SR-16326; Grand Daddy I.U. (Box 282)
          Catalog # 0-21823; A-side Matrix # 0-21823-A-SR1
        - Grand Funk Railroad - Closer to home, 1980; SR-16327; Grand Funk Railroad (Box 282)
          Catalog # SN-16176; A-side Matrix # SN-1-16176 G7
        - Grand Funk Railroad - Live album (Disc one), 1970; SR-16328; Grand Funk Railroad (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16329. Different discs.
          Catalog # SWBB-633; A-side Matrix # SWBB-1-633-1-W1
        - Grand Funk Railroad - Live album (Disc one), 1970; SR-16329; Grand Funk Railroad (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16328. Different discs.
          Catalog # SWBB-633; A-side Matrix # SWBB-1-633-1-H1
        - Grand Funk Railroad - Live album (Disc two), 1970; SR-16330; Grand Funk Railroad (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16331. Different discs.
          Catalog # SWBB-633; A-side Matrix # SWBB-3-633-2-W1
        - Grand Funk Railroad - Live album (Disc two), 1970; SR-16331; Grand Funk Railroad (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16330. Different discs.
          Catalog # SWBB-633; A-side Matrix # SWBB-3-633-J1
        - Grand Funk Railroad - Mark, Don & Mel 1969-71 (Disc one), 1972; SR-16332; Grand Funk Railroad (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16333. Double album.
          Catalog # SABB-11042; A-side Matrix # SABB-1-11042
        - Grand Funk Railroad - Mark, Don & Mel 1969-71 (Disc two), 1972; SR-16333; Grand Funk Railroad (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16332. Double album.
          Catalog # SABB-11042; A-side Matrix # SABB-3-11042
        - Grand Duke Bo Fresh - Rough rugged and raw, 1995; SR-16334; Grand Duke Bo Fresh (Box 282)
          Catalog # 12-PO 311; A-side Matrix # 12-PO-311-A
          Lyons Gate Records
        - Grand Master Jay - Where u at!!; Crowd control, 1997; SR-16335; Grand Master Jay; Her Royal Eminence (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16336. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # GMJ-0101; A-side Matrix # GMJ-0101-A
          GMJ International Entertainment
          Fayetteville, North Carolina
        - Grand Master Jay - Where u at!!; Crowd control, 1997; SR-16336; Grand Master Jay; Her Royal Eminence (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16335. Multiple copies.
        - Grand Puba - I like it (I wanna be where you are), 1995; SR-16337; Grand Puba (Box 282)
          Catalog # ED 5745; A-side Matrix # STED-5745-A-2
        - Grand Puba - Check it out, 1992; SR-16338; Grand Puba (Box 282)
          Catalog # ED 5646; A-side Matrix # ST-ED -5646-A2
        - Grand Rapmasters - Jingle bells; Deck the halls, 1992; SR-16339; Grand Rapmasters; Afrika Bambaataa; MC G.L.O.B.E.; Pow Wow (Box 282)
          Catalog # ESL-7055; A-side Matrix # ESL-7055A
          Essex Entertainment, Inc.
          Hackensack, New Jersey
        - Grand Rapmasters - Jingle bells; Deck the halls, 1992; SR-16340; Grand Rapmasters; Afrika Bambaataa; MC G.L.O.B.E.; Pow Wow (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16341. Multiple copies.
        - Grand Rapmasters - Jingle bells; Deck the halls, 1992; SR-16341; Grand Rapmasters; Afrika Bambaataa; MC G.L.O.B.E.; Pow Wow (Box 282)
          In same jacket as # SR-16340. Multiple copies.
        - Grand Rapmasters - Jingle bells; Deck the halls, 1992; SR-16342; Grand Rapmasters; Afrika Bambaataa; MC G.L.O.B.E.; Pow Wow (Box 282)
        - Grande, João - João Oliveira dos santos, 1989; SR-16343; Grande, João (Box 282)
          Catalog # 803.874; A-side Matrix # 803.874-A
          Programa Nacional De Copoeira
        - Grandaddy Souf - Run it, 2005; SR-16344; Grandaddy Souf; Get Cool (Box 282)
          Catalog # UNIR 21431-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR214311A
        - Grandmaster Caz - MC delight (Casanova's revenge), 2000; SR-16345; Grandmaster Caz (Box 282)
          Catalog # JC005; A-side Matrix # JC 005-A
          Jazz Child Records
        - Grandmaster Caz - Yvette, 1985; SR-16346; Grandmaster Caz (Box 282)
          Catalog # TUF 120010; A-side Matrix # TUF 120010 A
          Long Island City, New York
        - Grandmaster Caz - Grandmaster Caz (captain of the legendary Cold Crush Brothers), 1999; SR-16347; Grandmaster Caz; DJ Parker Lee (Box 282)
          Catalog # JC004; A-side Matrix # JC-004-A
        - Grandmaster Caz - MC delight (Casanova's revenge), 2000; SR-16348; Grandmaster Caz (Box 282)
        - Grandmaster Caz - Grandmaster Caz (captain of the legendary Cold Crush Brothers), 1999; SR-16349; Grandmaster Caz; DJ Parker Lee (Box 282)
        - Grandmaster Caz - The grandest of them all, 1992; SR-16350; Grandmaster Caz (Box 282)
          Catalog # TUF LP 0566; A-side Matrix # TUFLP-0566-A
        - Grandmaster Caz - MC delight (casanova's revenge), 2000; SR-16351; Grandmaster Caz (Box 282)
        - Grandmaster Chicken & D.J. Duck - Check out the chicken, 1989; SR-16352; Grandmaster Chicken & D.J. Duck (Box 283)
          Catalog # 874 603-1; A-side Matrix # 850 874603
          Spain
        - Grandmaster Flash - Style (Peter Gunn theme), 1986; SR-16353; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          Catalog # ED 5134; A-side Matrix # STED-66857-A-1
        - Grandmaster Flash - Alternate groove, 1985; SR-16354; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          Catalog # ED 5079; A-side Matrix # STED-5079-A-1
        - Grandmaster Flash - Superappin', 1979; SR-16355; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16356. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # EN 6001; A-side Matrix # 1103
          Enjoy Records
        - Grandmaster Flash - Superappin', 1979; SR-16356; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16355. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - Girls love the way he spins, 1985; SR-16357; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          Catalog # ED 5052; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66908-A-1
        - Grandmaster Flash - New York New York, 1983; SR-16358; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grand Master Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16359. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SH 457; A-side Matrix # VID-255-A
          Sugar Hill Records
        - Grandmaster Flash - New York New York, 1983; SR-16359; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grand Master Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16358. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - The official adventures of Grandmaster Flash sampler, 2002; SR-16360; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          Catalog # 12STRUT 010; A-side Matrix # 12STRUT010-A2
          Strut
        - Grandmaster Flash - Girls love the way he spins, 1985; SR-16361; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          Catalog # 0-66908; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66908-A-1
        - Grandmaster Flash - All wrapped up, 1987; SR-16362; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          Catalog # ED 5233; A-side Matrix # STED-66801-A-1
        - Grandmaster Flash and Furious Five - The message, 1982; SR-16363; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grand Master Flash & The Furious Five; Melle Mel; Duke Bootee (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16364. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SH-584; A-side Matrix # VID-235 AXXX
        - Grandmaster Flash and Furious Five - The message, 1982; SR-16364; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grand Master Flash & The Furious Five; Melle Mel; Duke Bootee (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16363. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - U know what time it is, 1987; SR-16365; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16566. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 0-66825; A-side Matrix # STED-66825A-1
        - Grandmaster Flash - U know what time it is, 1987; SR-16366; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16565. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - Scorpio, 1982; SR-16367; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16368. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SH 590; A-side Matrix # VID-241-A
        - Grandmaster Flash - Scorpio, 1982; SR-16368; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16367. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - White lines (don't don't do it), 1983; SR-16369; Grandmaster Flash; Grandmaster & Melle Mel (Box 283)
          Catalog # SH 465; A-side Matrix # VID-265-A
        - Grandmaster Flash - Girls love the way he spins, 1985; SR-16370; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16371. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - Girls love the way he spins, 1985; SR-16371; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16370. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - Behind closed doors, 1986; SR-16372; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16373. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # ED 5154; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66842-A1
        - Grandmaster Flash - Behind closed doors, 1986; SR-16373; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16372. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - Flash to the beat, 1982; SR-16374; Grandmaster Flash (Box 283)
          Catalog # SH-574; A-side Matrix # VTD-222-A
        - Grandmaster Flash - The message, 1982; SR-16375; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16376. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SH 268; A-side Matrix # VID-326-A
        - Grandmaster Flash - The message, 1982; SR-16376; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16375. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - The message; It's nasty (genius of love), 1993; SR-16377; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16378. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # HCL 2261; A-side Matrix # HCL-2261-A
          Hot Classics
        - Grandmaster Flash - The message; It's nasty (genius of love), 1993; SR-16378; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash & The Furious Five (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16377. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - On the strength, 1988; SR-16379; Grandmaster Flash; Furious Five; Grandmaster Flash And The Furious Five (Box 283)
          Catalog # 60769-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60769ADMM-2
        - Grandmaster Freshh - De American dream, 1986; SR-16380; Grandmaster Freshh (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16381. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SB 008; A-side Matrix # SB-008-A
          Street Beat Records
          Westville, New Jersey
        - Grandmaster Freshh - De American dream, 1986; SR-16381; Grandmaster Freshh (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16380. Multiple copies.
        - Grandmaster Slice - Strokin' 2000, 1999; SR-16382; Grandmaster Slice (Box 283)
          Catalog # WS 00051; A-side Matrix # WS-00051-A-1A
          Wingspan Records
          Danville, Virginia
        - Grandmaster Slice - Strokin' 2000, 1999; SR-16383; Grandmaster Slice (Box 283)
        - GrandMixer DXT - Crazy cuts, 1983; SR-16384; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16385. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 695; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-45712-45711-1
          Olyphant, Pennsylvania
        - GrandMixer DXT - Crazy cuts, 1983; SR-16385; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16384. Different discs. Not in discogs
        - GrandMixer DXT - Crazy cuts, 1983; SR-16386; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
          Catalog # Celluloid 8319; A-side Matrix # 8319 A
          Celluloid
        - GrandMixer DXT - Home of hip hop, 1985; SR-16387; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
          Catalog # CEL 185; A-side Matrix # CEL-185-A
        - GrandMixer DXT - Mean machine, 1984; SR-16388; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
          Catalog # CEL 174; A-side Matrix # CEL-174-A
        - GrandMixer DXT - Megamix II: why is it fresh?, 1984; SR-16389; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
          Catalog # CEL 173; A-side Matrix # CEL-173-A
        - GrandMixer DXT - Megamix II: why is it fresh?, 1984; SR-16390; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
        - GrandMixer DXT - Rock the house in Japan, 1986; SR-16391; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
          Catalog # 49 05964; A-side Matrix # XSS-175455-1D
        - GrandMixer DXT - Homme of hip hop, 1985; SR-16392; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
        - GrandMixer DXT - Megamix II: why is it fresh?, 1984; SR-16393; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 283)
        - GrandMixer DXT - Grand mixer (cuts it up), SR-16394; GrandMixer DXT; Grandmixer DST; Infinity Rappers (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16395. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # AZ/0-158; A-side Matrix # A-0158-A
          Disc' AZ International
        - GrandMixer DXT - Grand mixer (cuts it up), SR-16395; GrandMixer DXT; Grandmixer DST; Infinity Rappers (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16394. Multiple copies.
        - Grandsinister Ice - Sistrunk, 1987; SR-16396; Grandsinister Ice; DJ Pistal Pee (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16397. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # TH 001; A-side Matrix # TH-001-A
          Turf Handler
          Fort Lauderdale, Florida
        - Grandsinister Ice - Sistrunk, 1987; SR-16397; Grandsinister Ice; DJ Pistal Pee (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16396. Multiple copies.
        - Grant, Amy - Ungaurded, 1985; SR-16398; Grant, Amy (Box 283)
          Catalog # SP 5060; A-side Matrix # SPO 5060-A-RE1-RCA1
        - Grant, Angel - Lil' red boat, 1998; SR-16399; Grant, Angel (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16400. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # U12-56176; A-side Matrix # U8P-1257A
        - Grant, Angel - Lil' red boat, 1998; SR-16400; Grant, Angel (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16399. Multiple copies.
        - Grant, David - Stop and go (master mix), 1983; SR-16401; Grant, David (Box 283)
          Catalog # GRANX 1; A-side Matrix # GRANX 1 A-1
        - Grant, Eddy - Dance party (extended version), 1986; SR-16402; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          Catalog # 4R9-05938; A-side Matrix # XSS-175301-1A
          Portrait
        - Grant, Eddy - Going for broke, 1984; SR-16403; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          Catalog # ICELP 6001; A-side Matrix # B-1116 A-1
          ICE
        - Grant, Eddy - Say I love you, 1977; SR-16404; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          Catalog # ICE-143; A-side Matrix # GS ICE DISCO 143
        - Grant, Eddy - File under rock, 1988; SR-16405; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          Catalog # 064-79 0343 1; A-side Matrix # 7903431-A1
          Europe
        - Grant, Eddy - Gimme hope Jo'Anna, 1988; SR-16406; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          Catalog # ICE 12 8701; A-side Matrix # ICE-12-8701 A1
        - Grant, Eddy - Dance party (extended version), 1986; SR-16407; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
        - Grant, Eddy - Till I can't take love no more (extended version), 1983; SR-16408; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16409. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # ICE T 60; A-side Matrix # ICET 60 A-3U-1-1
        - Grant, Eddy - Till I can't take love no more (extended version), 1983; SR-16409; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16408. Multiple copies.
        - Grant, Eddy - Eddy Grant (Disc one), 1981; SR-16410; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)